피비, 창가에 있는 저 남자
좀 봐!
Phoebe. Will you check out that guy
by the window. Wow!
뒤에 저 남자? 엄청 작은데
게다가 혼자 중얼중얼해
That guy back there? He's awfully short.
And I think he's talking to himself.
솔직히 말하자면
침대에서도 별로야
And to be completely honest,
he's not that good in bed.
정말?
Really?
요즘 내가 왜 이러지?
모든 남자한테 다 이래
What is wrong with me lately?
It's like, every guy I see.
저 남자 좀 봐
I mean, look at that guy, for example.
평소엔 내 타입이 아니잖아
That's not someone
I would be attracted to.
근데 지금은...
But right now,
with the way I'm feeling..
바지를 찢어 제치고
싶어 미칠 지경이야
all I want to do is rip off his sweatpants
and fanny pack.
지금 임신 4개월째지?
Wait a second! This is about the fourth
month of your pregnancy, right?
- 응
- 그럼 아주 정상이야
-Yeah.
-This is completely normal.
그때쯤 호르몬이 미쳐 날뛰거든
Around the fourth month,
your hormones start going crazy.
- 정말? 너도 그랬어?
- 그럼!
-Really? So this has happened to you?
-Absolutely!
게다가 난 세 쌍둥이였다구
And keep in mind now,
I was carrying triplets.
의학적으로 말하면
세 배나 더 밝혔다 이거지
So in medical terms,
I was thrice as randy.
그렇구나!
Wow, this explains so much!
지난주에 가게마다 돌면서
산타 무릎에 앉아 있었잖아
Last weekend, I went from store to store,
sitting on Santas' laps.
난 풋로커의 에반더 홀리필드
Yeah, I remember trying
to steal a cardboard cutout..
마네킹을 훔쳤잖아
of Evander Holyfield
from a Foot Locker.
내일 의사한테 가서
물어봐야겠다
Well, I go see my doctor tomorrow.
I'll ask her about this.
약 같은 걸 줄지도 모르지
Maybe she can give me a pill
or something.
맞아, 너한테는 약이 필요해
Yeah, that's what you need.
A good pill.
키 작고 미친 남자가 나한테
아는 척 해, 내가 미쳐
Oh, no. Short, crazy guy recognizes me.
Worst mistake of my life.
전화해
Call me.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'로스의 발전'
록펠러 센터에서 찍은
사진 찾았어
I got our pictures developed
from Rockefeller Center.
나랑 모나랑 스케이트 타는
사진 볼래?
Great. Hey, Joey, want to check out
pictures of me and Mona ice-skating?
그러고 싶지만
지금 무지 바빠서
Ordinarily, I would love to,
but I am just swamped right now.
그 이상한 프레첼 파는 사람이
찍어준 사진 어딨지?
Where are the pictures that that creepy
pretzel vendor took of us together?
아마 뒤에 있을 걸
Oh, yeah.
Probably at the end.
세상에! 전부 내 가슴만
찍어 놨잖아
Oh, my God! All he took were pictures
of my breasts.
사진 같이 보자구?
I'm missing picture time!
로스, 모나도 얼굴이 있어
You know, she has a face, Ross.
나 아냐, 난 카메라에
줌 렌즈 있는 것도 몰랐다구
I didn't take these, okay? I didn't even
know my camera had a zoom lens.
"용서해주세요, 경관님"
"Comma, officer."
- 여기 잘 나온 사진 있다
- 와, 정말이네!
-Okay, here's a good one of us.
-Wow, that is a good one!
크리스마스 카드 같아
It looks like a holiday card.
가운데 나무가 있고
눈 맞으며 스케이트 타는 사람들
With the tree in the middle
and the skaters and the snow.
고마워요, 프레첼 변태 아저씨
Good job, pretzel pervert.
해마다 카드를 보내고 싶었는데
한 번도 못했어
Every year, I say I'm gonna send out
holiday cards and I never do it.
우리 이 사진 같이 보낼까?
Do you want
to send this one out together?
같이? 다른 사람들한테?
Together? Like, to people?
"즐거운 크리스마스 보내세요
모나와 로스 드림" 어때?
Yeah. "Happy holidays, from Mona
and Ross." It'll be cute, okay?
좋아
Okay.
- 일하러 가야겠다, 나중에 전화해?
- 알았어
-I gotta get to work. Call me later?
-Sure, sure.
- 안녕
- 잘 가
-Bye, guys.
-Bye.
축하해! 방금 결혼한 거!
Congratulations! You just got married!
좀 이상하지?
I know. Can you believe that?
왜 함께 카드를 보내고
싶어하는 거야?
I'm sorry. What's the big deal
about a holiday card?
카드는 결혼한 사람들이나
가족들이 보내는 거지
Married couples send out cards.
Families send out cards.
두 달 데이트한 사람들은
안 보내는 거야
People who have been dating for
a couple of months don't send out cards.
- 모나 왜 그러지, 미쳤나?
- 입 조심해, 네 와이프잖아!
-What is she, crazy?
-That's your wife you're talking about!
심각해, 이건 우리 관계가
크게 변하는 거야
No, really. I mean,
that would be like a huge step forward.
난 지금이 좋아
I like things just the way they are.
이제서야 정상 속도로
가고 있다구
I'm finally in a relationship
that's not moving too fast.
알지? 보통 때 같으면
지금쯤 이혼할 시간이야
You know, ordinarily,
I'd be divorced by now.
그럼 싫다고 해
모나가 어떻게 나올까?
Okay, so just tell her you don't wanna
send out the card. What's she gonna do?
이거
This.
부담 주려던 거는 아니었어
Oh, okay. I didn't mean
to put pressure on you..
그냥 같이 하면 재미있겠다고
생각한 거야
I just thought it would be something fun
for us to do together..
하지만 괜찮아, 정말
but okay, that's okay.
하긴 자기 말대로 별 일 아니지
카드 같이 보내자
Okay, stop. Stop. You're right,
it's not that big a deal. I'll do the card.
- 뭐? 카드 같이 보내자구 했어
- 알아, 그냥...
-What? I said I'd do it.
-I know, it's just..
20불 가져도 돼?
Can I have $20?
- 점심 먹으러 갈까?
- 잠깐만
-Hi. You ready for lunch?
-One second.
- 귀엽다
- 빙! 그리고 빙부인!
-That's cute.
-Bing! And the Bingette!
어쩐지 사무실이 후끈하더라
I thought it felt a little hotter
in the office today.
- 우리 사장님 알지?
- 안녕하세요
-Oh, honey, you remember my boss, Doug.
-Yes. Hi.
좋은 소식! 이혼 쫑냈어
오전에 도장 찍었지
Good news! The divorce is final.
I signed the papers this a.m.
이혼하신 줄 몰랐어요
유감입니다
I didn't know you and Kara divorced.
I'm sorry.
유감?
마침내 덫에서 풀려난 거야
Sorry? I finally chewed my leg out
of that bear trap.
- 암튼 자네들은 축하해
- 저희는 아무일 없습니다
-Congratulations to you guys, though.
-No leg-chewing for us, sir.
두고 보자구
Well, give it time.
이혼하고 결혼하고
축하할 일이 많구만
So the divorce, the marriage,
we got a lot to celebrate.
내일 함께 저녁이나 하세
How about we all go out
to dinner tomorrow night.
변명 거리가 전혀 생각 안나
I can't think
of anything we're doing.
도대체 왜 생각이 안나는 거야?
Why can't I think
of anything we're doing?
내일 6시까지는 법원 일이
끝날거야
Tomorrow night it is.
I should be out of court by 6.
계속 나한테 성희롱 혐의를
씌우는데
They keep throwing sexual harassment
cases at me..
내가 한 방씩 먹이고 있지!
and I keep knocking them
out of the park!
내일 뵐게요
Okay, see you tomorrow.
내일 안 만날거야
Just so you know,
we're not seeing him tomorrow.
저 사람은 알수록 더 이상해
Honey, once you get to know him,
he's much, much worse.
혼자는 싫어
I can't do this alone.
미안하지만 저 사람하고는
하루도 더 같이 못 있겠어
Honey, I'm sorry. I can't help you. I can't
spend another evening with that man.
결혼식 때 저 사람이 어땠는지
기억나?
Do you remember how he behaved
at our wedding?
우리가 초대 안해서 그런 거야
That's because he wasn't invited.
약혼식 때 이상하게 행동해서
Because of the way he behaved
at our engagement party.
맞다! 오줌이 얼음 조각을
그대로 관통해, 그렇지?
Oh, yeah! Urine cuts right through
an ice sculpture, doesn't it?
모르겠다, B 플러스
Oh, what the hell? B plus.
사진 가게에 들렀는데
이거 봐봐
Hi! I went by the photo shop.
Take a look.
우리 카드 샘플이야
어때?
Here is a mockup of our card.
What do you think?
와우, 좋다
Wow, that's great.
"사랑하는 로스와 모나로부터"
라고 쓸까?
Do you think it should say,
"Love, Ross and Mona"?
아직 서로 사랑한다는 말을
안 했는데
Well, we haven't said that
to each other yet..
다른 사람들한테는
할 수 있잖아
but I guess it's okay
to say it to other people.
- 몇 장 쓸거야? 난 100장
- 100장?
-How many did you want? I'll get 100.
-A hundred?
글쎄, 나는...
Well, I guess I'll take..
모나?
Mona?
실은 카드 보내는 거
좀 꺼려져
I'm not sure
about the whole card thing.
정말? 왜?
Really? Why not?
함께 카드를 보낸다는 게...
Sending out a holiday card together?
우리 관계가 그 단계인지
잘 모르겠어
I just don't know
if we're really quite there yet.
그 생각은 미처 못했네
자기 말이 맞아
I didn't think of it that way.
You're right.
- 그럼 하나 물어봐도 돼?
- 응
-So can I ask you a question?
-Yeah.
우린 어느 단계야?
Where are we?
우리 관계가 어디쯤 가고
있는 거야?
You know, where are we?
Where is this relationship going?
자기랑 같이 있는 게 좋아
그리고 계속 발전하길 바라고
I love spending time with you.
I just hope we're moving forward.
이야기를 좀 하자
We should talk about that,
don't you think?
그냥 카드 보내자!
Let's do the card!
- 뭐?
- 카드! 보내도 될 거 같아!
-What?
-The card! I think we're there!
그래, 근데 이야기는 해야지
Okay. But I still think
we should have this conversation.
정말?
Really?
카드 보내는데두?
Even with the card?
롱 선생님은 오늘 안 계시고
쉬프 선생님께서 보십니다
Just so you know, Dr. Long can't be here
today, so Dr. Schiff will be seeing you.
하나 물어봐도 되요?
Oh, okay.
Can I ask you a question?
제 피 뽑은 남자
귀엽지 않나요?
Was it me, or was the guy
who took my blood sample really cute?
누구 말하는지 아시죠?
대머리에 털복숭이 남자
You know who I'm talking about?
Bowl haircut, hairy fingers?
신경 쓰지 마세요
혼잣말 한 거예요
Actually, never mind.
I just answered my own question.
- 안녕하세요? 쉬프 박사입니다
- 그러시군요
-Hi, Rachel? I'm Dr. Schiff.
-Yes, you are.
- 이 사람은 귀여운 거 맞죠?
- 그렇고 말고
-Okay, now he's cute, right?
-Oh, God, yes.
어떠세요?
So, how's it going?
아주 좋아요
이제 제 이야기는 그만 하구요
It's going really good.
But enough about me! Come on.
어디 출신이에요?
뭐 하세요?
Where are you from?
What do you do?
- 의산데요
- 그렇지, 제 말은...
-I'm a doctor.
-Right. I meant..
여가시간에요
요리하세요? 스키 타세요?
in your spare time.
Do you cook? So you ski?
아님 부인이나 여자친구랑
지내세요?
Or just hang out with your wife,
or girlfriend?
부인이나 여자친구는 없지만
스키는 좋아하죠
I don't have a wife or a girlfriend,
but I do like to ski.
저두요!
정말 우연의 일치네요
I love to ski!
How amazing is this?
- 불편한 데 있으세요?
- 아뇨, 아주 편한데요
-Are you experiencing any discomfort?
-No, I'm very comfortable.
- 방귀 때문에 힘들지 않아요?
- 아뇨!
-Any painful gas?
-No!
쉬프 선생님!
무슨 그런 질문을 하세요?
Dr. Schiff!
What kind of question is that?
테이블에 누우시겠어요?
Okay, then. Would you like
to lie down on the table?
제가 그러길 원하세요?
Would you like me
to lie down on the table?
- 분위기가 좀 이상하네요
- 선생님도 그렇게 느끼세요?
-Is there something going on here?
-Do you feel it too?
- 나 왔어
- 어땠어?
-Hi.
-How did your doctor's appointment go?
오늘은 "잘생긴 남자"
선생이었는데
Well, let's see,
they gave me "cute boy" doctor today.
진찰 중에 내가 새끼 손가락을
그 사람 턱에 갖다 댔어
In the middle of the exam,
I put my pinkie in his chin dimple.
- 저런!
- 왜 그랬어?
-Oh, my God!
-Why did you do that?
임신 4개월때 내가 어땠는지
기억해?
Remember that little problem I was having
during my fourth month of pregnancy?
에반더 홀리필드를 어찌 잊겠어
Oh, yeah!
The Evander Holyfield phase.
굶주리다 못해 나한테까지
덤볐잖아
Oh, man! You were so hard up,
you practically came on to me.
설마
You wish.
내가 원했으면 할 수도 있었어
Hey, I could have had you
if I wanted you.
그래? 그럼 지금 해봐
Oh, yeah? Come and get it.
제발, 이것도 난 흥분돼
나 정말 심각해
Okay, even this is turning me on.
You guys, I got problems.
로스!
모나랑 어떻게 되고 있어?
Oh, hey. Hey, Ross!
How's it going with you and Mona?
아직도 사귀니?
Are you guys still together?
응, 관계를 발전시키고 있어
카드도 함께 보낼거야
Yeah, we're moving forward.
You'll be getting our card.
연말 카드를 함께 보내?
You're doing a holiday card?
카드 뿐이 아냐
모나가 대화도 하재
We're not just doing a card.
She also wants to have the conversation..
우리 관계의 방향에 대해서...
about where the relationship
is going.
여자들이란!
Women!
여자들은 도대체 왜
대화를 원하는 거야?
I know! Why do you guys need
to have this conversation?
자존심 없는 남자나 그런 걸 묻지
"우리 어떤 사이야?"
No self-respecting man would ask a woman,
"So where is this going?"
너 나한테 그렇게 물었잖아
Ross, you asked me that.
넌 정말 속을 알 수 없었어
내가 독심술사냐!
You were a closed book, okay?
I'm not a mind reader!
모나한테 뭐라고 할거야?
이 관계가 어디로 가는 거야?
What are you gonna say to her?
Where is this relationship going?
몰라, 정말 좋아하고
사귀고 싶은 건 맞는데
I don't know. I really like her
and I wanna keep dating her.
- 그렇게 말해
- 안돼
-So tell her that.
-No, I can't.
그럼 이럴 거야
"아무데도 안가는 거네"
Because then she's gonna say,
"Well, it's not moving anywhere..
- "그냥 헤어져"
- 하긴 그렇다
-then we should just break up."
-Yeah, that's true.
그리고 난 그런 대화 정말 싫어
자신 없어
Besides, I hate those conversations.
I'm horrible at them. Really.
몸짓으로 표현해 볼까...
Maybe I need some kind of a gesture..
관계가 진전되고 있다는 걸
말없이 몸으로 표현하는 거지
something that says we're moving
forward without having to talk about it.
동거하자고?
Like asking her
to move in with you?
그거 보다는 약하게
Smaller than that.
- 음악 테이프 만들어 주는 거?
- 그거 보다는 세게
-Making her a mix tape?
-Bigger than that.
- 아파트 열쇠를 줘
- 음악 테이프 이야기하고 있었잖아
-Give her a key to your apartment.
-We were closer with the mix tape.
"사랑해"라고 말했어?
사랑한다고 해
Have you said, "I love you"?
You could say, "I love you."
그 단계인지 아직 잘 모르겠어
I don't think I'm quite there yet.
하지만 "함께 있어서 좋아"
라고는 할 수 있어
But I could say,
"I love spending time with you."
- 여자들은 그 말 싫어해
- 뺨 맞는 거랑 같애
-We hate that.
-That is a slap in the face.
모르겠다
그냥 대화를 해야겠어
Forget it. You know what?
I'll just have the conversation.
지금 이 상태가 좋고
잘 되길 원한다고 말할래
I'll just say I like things the way
they are, and hope for the best.
어떻게 생각해, 레이첼?
What do you think, Rach?
'약간만 더 추웠으면 도드라진'
I think if it was
a little colder in here..
'네 젖꼭지를 볼 텐데'라고
생각하고 있어
I could see your nipples
through that sweater.
빙? 오늘밤 8시야
Bing? We're all set for tonight, 8:00.
오늘은 모니카가
야근을 해서 안 되겠어요
As it turns out, we can't do it.
Monica has to work.
내 전부인은 일을 안했는데
My ex-wife didn't work.
자기 엄마로 변하는
일이라면 모를까
Unless you call turning
into her mother "work."
좋아, 그럼 내일 저녁
Fine. Tomorrow night then.
- 내일도 모니카가 안될 겁니다
- 왜?
-Tomorrow's no good for her, either.
-Why not?
체육대회...
It's the semifinals..
준결승전이 있어서요
of her bocce ball tournament.
그래, 그럼 그 다음날
Okay. The night after that then.
그 날은 결승전인데
모니카가 결승까지 갈 걸요
Well, that's the finals, and I think
she's gonna go all the way, sir.
도대체 왜 그래, 빙?
부인이 혹시 나를 싫어하나?
What's going on, Bing? Does your wife
have a problem with me or something?
무슨 그런 말도 안되는
말씀을
...
Well, now you're just talking crazy.
그런데 왜 셋이서 안 되는거야?
Then why can't the three of us
go out together?
왜냐면... 저희 헤어졌거든요
Because we split up.
모니카랑 저 헤어졌어요
Monica and I split up.
저 좀 도와주세요
Hold me.
이런... 짐작은 하고 있었네
Good God, Bing. Well, I can't say
I'm altogether surprised.
어쩐지 자넬 보는 눈빛에
사랑이 없더구만
I saw the way she looked at you,
and there was no love there.
그러고는 나를 아주 갈망하는
눈길로 쳐다봤어
And the way she looked at me,
pure lust.
정말 누구 목이라도
조르고 싶은 심정입니다
What would really help me through
this tough time is choking someone.
자네 맘 이해하네
I know how you feel. Oh, yeah.
한 여자에게 순정을 바쳤다가
I know what it's like to give a woman
all your love..
그 사랑이 모욕으로 돌아오는
기분을 내가 알지
and then have that love
thrown back in your face.
게다가 법원은 그 뚱뚱한
자식들에 대해 양육권을 줘
And then the court decides to give you
custody of those fat, left-handed twins.
아이들에게 좋은 아버지가 있어서
좋겠네요
Well, they're lucky to have you, sir.
빙, 내가 도와주겠네
Bing, my boy,
we're gonna get you over this.
코트 입게
스트립쇼나 보러 가세!
Here's the plan: Grab your coat,
we're going to a strip club!
안돼요!
모니카가 기절할 걸요
Oh, no!
Monica would freak.
그런 여자 지옥이나 가라죠!
But to hell with that bitch!
자
Here we go.
모나, 이제 우리 관계에 대해
이야기할 시간이야
Mona, it's time we had a conversation
about where things are with us.
내가 하자고 했잖아
Yeah, I think I suggested that.
우린 정말 통하는 게...
We are so..
난 자기 정말 좋아해
함께 있는 시간도 정말 좋구
Well, I really like you.
And I love hanging out with you.
그리고 정말 즐거워
And I'm having a lot of fun.
응
Okay.
그냥 재미만 있는 관계는
무의미하다는 거지
There's no point in spending time
with someone if it's just fun.
어딘가로 향해야 하잖아, 그렇지?
It's gotta be going somewhere, right?
그래서 어디로 가는 거냐
So where is it going?
이게 문제지
That's the real question.
그리고 답은...
And the answer is..
어딘가로 가는 거지...
it's going somewhere..
재미있는 곳으로...
fun.
자기가 무슨 생각하는지 알아
10년 전에는 재밌는 게 좋았지
I know what you're thinking.
Fun was fine for you 10 years ago.
하지만 이젠 젊지 안잖아
But you're not getting any younger.
아니! 내 말은 자기가 아니라...
자기말고
No! I mean, not you.
Not you.
자기는 점점 젊어지고 있어!
You are getting younger!
매 순간 젊어지는 것 같아
비결이 뭐야?
You're getting younger by the second.
What's your secret?
그래서 우리 관계가 어디 있다구?
I'm sorry, so where are we?
음, 결론적으로 말하면...
Well, to sum up..
우리는 재미있게 지내고
자기는 젊어 보이고
we're having fun.
You look young.
- 그래서...
- 하지만 그걸로는 부족하지
-Okay..
-But that's not enough.
그래서...
So..
내 아파트 열쇠 줄게
here's a key to my apartment.
- 정말?
- 정말
-Really?
-Really.
너무 빠른 거 같지 않아?
You don't think this is too fast?
아파트 열쇠를 줬다구?
You gave her a key
to your apartment?
그냥 열쇠가 아니라
유일한 열쇠를 줘버렸어!
Not just a key.
I gave her the only key!
이제 난 아주 깊은 관계에
빠진 노숙자야!
I am now a homeless person
in a very serious relationship!
- 열쇠를 왜 줬어?
- 코너로 몰렸거든, 됐어?
-Why did you give her a key?
-She talked me into a corner, okay?
모나는 대화의 마법사 같아
She's like this conversational wizard.
그래서 원치 않는 대화를 하고
So you had the conversation
you didn't wanna have..
안 하려던 행동을 했단 말이지
and you made the gesture
you didn't wanna make.
내가 "야, 오늘 나 굉장한
일 했어"라고 하든?
Did I start this by saying, "Hey,
I did something awesome today"?
- 혹시 우리 집 열쇠 가지고 있니?
- 우리한테 준 적 없잖아
-Do either of you have a key to my place?
-I don't think you've ever given us keys.
왜 그랬겠어? 내 집인데
Yeah, why would I? It's my home.
- 로스, 어떻게 됐어?
- 이제 길거리에서 살게 됐어
-Ross, how did the conversation go?
-Great. I live on the street.
어느 길인데?
Where?
- 안녕
- 모니카, 레이첼
-Hi.
-Okay, Monica, Rachel..
- 내 친구 로저야
- 안녕하세요
-this is my friend Roger.
-Hi, Roger.
음료수 좀 가져올게
도와줄래?
I'll get us some drinks.
Could you help me?
그래
Yeah, okay.
저 사람 너랑 섹스 하러 온 거야
He's here to have sex with you.
- 뭐라구?
- 고마워 안해도 돼
-What?
-You're welcome.
- 피비, 싫어!
- 괜찮아, 아직 숫총각이야
-Phoebe, no!
-It's okay. He's a virgin.
레이첼, 이 남자가 너랑
섹스 한다는데
Rachel, I was talking to this guy.
I think he'll have sex with you.
두 사람만 남겨두고 가자
Let's leave these two alone.
싫어! 호르몬이 어쩌든
아무하고나 잘 수는 없어!
No! I don't care what my hormones are
doing! I won't do it with some random guy!
좋아! 그럼 네가 말해
저 사람 진짜 기대가 컸거든!
Fine! Then you tell Roger, because
he was really looking forward to this!
빙! 저 쌍둥이 자매들을 봐
Bing! Look at those twin sisters
dancing together.
내가 특별히 랩댄스
주문해 줄게
Let me buy you a lap dance
with those girls.
괜찮습니다
그리고 한 명인데요
That's all right, sir.
And that's just one girl.
- 빙, 이게 뭔가?
- 손이요
-Bing, what's this?
-It's a hand.
잭과 코크 손잡이로
사용하시는 거잖아요
It's a thing you use
as a Jack and Coke holder.
결혼반지잖아, 빼버려
이스트강에 던져 버리자구!
It's a wedding ring. Get rid of it.
We'll throw it in the East River!
- 싫어요!
- 버려!
-No!
-Yes!
난 그러니까 속이 후련하더군
갈매기 머리를 맞출 수도 있어
I did it, and I felt a lot better! You
might even hit a seagull in the head.
좋아요, 여분의 열쇠가 많이
필요해요
Okay. I'm gonna need a bunch
of extra keys.
아무 이유없이 줘버리는
버릇이 있어서요
Apparently, I give them away
for no reason at all.
로스, 무슨 일이야?
자물쇠를 바꿨어?
Ross, what's going on?
You're changing the lock?
아니
No.
저 남자가 한 거야
That guy is.
나한테 아파트 열쇠 주고 나서
자물쇠를 바꿔?
You give me a key to your apartment,
and then you change the lock?
행운을 비네, 친구
Good luck, buddy.
왜 이렇게 날 혼동시키는 거야
I thought we were moving forward. Now
you're sending me all these mixed signals.
도대체 하고 싶은 말이 뭐야?
What are you trying to tell me?
하고 싶은 말이 뭐냐면...
I'm trying to tell you..
내가 음악 테이프 만들어 줬지
I made you a mix tape.
- 뭐라구?
- 사랑해
-What?
-I love you.
난 자기랑 함께 있어서 좋아
And I love spending time with you.
- 자기, 나 왔어
- 테킬라 공장 갔다 왔어?
-Hi, honey, I'm home.
-From the tequila factory?
죽는 줄 알았어
It was awful.
더그한테서 빠져 나오려고
우리가 헤어졌다고 했어
To get out of going to dinner with Doug,
I told him you and I split up.
그러니까 스트립 클럽에
데려가는 거야
So then he took me to these strip clubs
and sleazy bars.
내가 결혼반지 안 버리니까
새한테 깡통을 던졌어
When I wouldn't give him my wedding
ring, he threw a soda can at a bird.
이리와
입으로 숨 셔야겠다
Come here.
I can breathe through my mouth.
- 응
- 최악이 뭐였는 줄 알아?
-Oh, sweetie.
-You know what the worst part was?
자기 없으면 내 인생도
그렇게 될 것 같았어
I got to see what my life
would be like without you.
랩댄스와 함께 한
인생은 아름다워라고
It was like It's a Wonderful Life
with lap dances.
언제나 내 곁에 있겠다고
약속해 줘
Please promise me
that you'll never leave me..
나랑 함께 늙어가고
인생을 함께 보내겠다고
that we'll grow old together, and be
with each other for the rest of our lives.
약속할게
I promise.
그래서 말인데, 올해 연말 카드
함께 보내는 게 어때?
Speaking of together, how about
we send out a holiday card this year?
아직 그 정도는 아닌거 같은데
I don't know if we're there yet.
피자 시키려고 하는데요
하나 물어봐도 되요?
I'd like to order a pizza.
Can I ask you a question?
귀여운 금발 총각이 배달하나요?
"아베크롬비 & 피치" 옷 입는?
Is the cute blond guy delivering tonight?
Very "Abercrombie & Fitch."
- 다시 전화할게요
- 누구야?
-I'll call you back.
-Who was that?
- 피자 가게
- 피자 가게 전화를 끊었어?
-It's just the pizza place.
-You hung up on the pizza place?
난 네 친구들 전화 안 끊잖아
I don't hang up on your friends.
- 미안, 오늘 좀 힘들어서 그래
- 무슨 일 있어?
-Sorry, honey, I'm just having a rough day.
-What's wrong?
- 듣고 싶지 않을거야
- 내가 물어봤잖아
-You don't want to hear about it.
-Then why did I ask?
좀 당황스러운 이야기야
임신 때문에 말이야...
Okay, this is really embarrassing, but
lately, with this whole pregnancy thing..
내가 좀...
I'm just finding myself..
뭐랄까...
How do I put this?
성적으로 강렬해졌거든
Erotically charged.
발정 났다는 말이야?
Is that college talk for "horny"?
응, 그 감정들을 주체할 수가
없는게 문제야
Yeah. I have all of these feelings,
and I don't know what to do about them.
심각한 관계는 싫으니깐
그냥 데이트도 못하고
I can't date like a normal person, which is
fine because I don't need a relationship.
그저 황홀한 하룻밤이 필요해
섹스만 원한다구
All I really want is one great night!
Just sex.
구속이나 관계는 원치 않아
No strings attached.
No relationship.
편하게 날 이해하는 사람과
With someone I feel comfortable with,
and who knows what he's doing.
딱 하룻밤만 황홀하게 보내는 게
For just one great night.
I mean, is that really so hard..
그렇게 힘든 걸까?
to find?
너는 오늘 어땠어?
So how was your day?
좋았어, 큰 비둘기도 보고
Good. I saw a pretty big pigeon.
내일 일찍 일어나야 해
벌써... 7시가 다 됐네
Well, I gotta get up early,
and it's almost 7:00.
- 방에 갈래
- 잘 자!
-I gotta go to my room.
-Good night!
너도!
Good night!
- 난 못해 줘!
- 해달라고 안했어!
-I can't do it!
-I didn't ask you to do it!
- 넌 레이첼이야!
- 넌 조이구!
-You're Rachel!
-You're Joey!
- 넌 내 친구야!
- 아주 친한 친구
-You're my friend!
-Right back at you.
그건 옳지 못해
이상하고 나쁜 짓이야!
Yeah. Plus, it would be wrong,
and weird and bad!
근데 왜 그래?
너한테 해달라고 안했어!
So bad! But I don't know what you're talking
about. I didn't ask you to do anything!
알아!
I know!
- 하고 싶어?
- 아니!
-You wanna do it?
-No!
- 그냥 시험해 본 거야!
- 이제 그만 이야기하자!
-I'm just testing you!
-Well, that's the end of this conversation!
- 없었던 걸로 해!
- 알았어!
-This conversation never happened!
-Never happened!
- 잘 자!
-Good night!
얼른 들어가!
Get back in there!
로저 일은 미안해
Listen, I'm sorry about
that whole thing with Roger.
내가 잘못했어, 그래서 보상으로
It really wasn't right.
And I want to make it up to you.
이걸 가져왔어
맘에 들길 바래
So I brought you something
I think you'll really enjoy.
이거 가지라고 주는 거 아냐
빌려 주는 거야
Now this is just a loan, okay?
I'm gonna want him back.
갈게
I'm gonna go now.
미안, 할 수 있다고 생각했는데
안되겠다
I'm sorry.
I thought I could do it, and I can't.